Zonta Club of Albany; Records apap399
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Zonta Club of Albany Records
1929-2022
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap399
9.6 cubic ft.
This collection documents the day-to-day activities of the Zonta Club of Albany, a service organization in the Captial Region of New York, comprised of executives, professionals, and businesswomen, as well as documenting the activities of the Club within Zonta International.
Content Description
The collection includes materials such as newsletters, meeting miinutes, member directories, club history, and records associated with the club's charitable activities both on a local and international scale.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is made up of three series that are arranged alphabetically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Club archivist Rita Cousino donated all materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenandner Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2022.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Historical Note
On May 27, 1929, 15 women met to plan the organization of a Zonta Club in Albany, New York. On October 30, 1929 the first women's service club in Albany officially became a Zonta Club. The Club is a member of the worldwide Zonta International which has 33,000 members in 1,242 clubs in 68 countries. The goal of the Club is to advance the status of women and girls. Zonta was founded in 1919 in Buffalo, New York.
Throughout its history, the Zonta Club of Albany has engaged in outreach, conducted fundraising, volunteered, and implemented projects to benefit Capital District women and girls. These efforts have included the building of an interfaith chapel at Memorial Hospital in Albany; contributing toward the formation of the Albany Girls Club; and supporting such local programs and organizations as Mercy House, The Next Step, Inc., Albany Medical Center, Albany County Jail Women's Project, the Capital City Rescue Mission's Women and Children's Center, the Equinox Domestic Violence Shelter, and many more. In addition, the Zonta Club of Albany participates in district and international award programs. Local awards include the Frances Wodward/Helena Roscoe Nursing Award and the Zelda Uthe Award given to a law student.
The Zonta Club of Albany also was instrumental in the establishment of other local Zonta clubs including ones in Troy, Montgomery/Fulton, Columbia/Greene, and Kingston.
Zonta Club of Albany (N.Y.); Zonta International; Women in nonprofit organizations--New York (State)--Albany; Albany, New York; Women; Neighborhood and Community Associations; New York (State)--Social conditions; Fundraising--New York (State)--Albany (N.Y.); Women in charitable work--New York (State)--Albany; Women--New York (State)--Albany--Societies and clubs; Minutes; Scrapbooks; Newsletters; Administrative records; Membership lists; Conference reports; Financial Records; Programs; Banners; Photographs
- Administration, 1929-2019; 1; 2.4 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  The Administrative series contains: an account book, budget and financial reports, by-laws, charters, correspondence relating to the administration of the Club, and meeting minutes. The materials provide information regarding the structure of the Club, how meetings were conducted, and the election of officers.
  - Account Book, 1929-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1963; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1968-1969; 1979-1985; 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget Reports, 1978-1980; 1983-2019 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bylaws, 1980-1988; 1990-1999; 2004-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Charters, 1929; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Club E-mails, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Club President Memo, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee Assignments, 1968-1969; 1999-2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Conference Report, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: District 2, 1969-1970; 1981-1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: International and National Administrative, 1969-1971; 1985-1987; 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 2 Officers, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Goals and Accomplishments, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Inter-City Meetings, 1959-1961; 1973-1975; 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Leadership and Resource Guide, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Manual of Procedure, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Manual of Procedures, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Manual of Procedures, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2019 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Membership, 1958; 1979-1988; 1991-1999; 2001-2018 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Membership and Classification Manual, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Memo: Voting, 1968; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Occupations Classification, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Organizational Chart, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Planning Meetings, 1985-2019; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Program Chair Report, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Service Reports, 1947-1949; 1982-1993; 2007-2016; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1964-1969; 1973; 1985-1988; 1996-1999; 2006-2019 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Workshop for Presidents, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Zonta Club Manual, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Subject Files, 1936-2022; 2; 4.8 cubic ft.
  The Subject series contains materials relating to the Club's history, member directories, photographs, conference and seminar materials, correspondence (thank you notes), and programs. The series also contains flat files and oversize boxes which house scrapbooks one of which documents the Clubs' involvement with the Memorial Chapel at Albany Memorial Hospital (now named Samaritan Hospital, Albany Memorial Campus), banners, and a sash. This series provides information about how the Club worked within the local community as well as with other area clubs.
  - Advocacy, 2007-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany Tricentennial, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albany Tricentennial: Newspaper, 1986 (Flat-file 1)
  - Alice Morgan Wright, 1975; 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amelia Earhart Fellowship Award, 1936-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anniversaries, 1946-1954; 1969-1979; 2009-2019 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Banner, Brown and Yellow, Undated (Oversize 1)
  - Capital City Rescue Mission, 2009; 2011; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Certificates of Appreciation, 1985; 2009-2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Charlotte Gray, 2000; 2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Club History, 1959-1969; 1979-1988; 1992-1998; 2007-2022; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Community Service, 1970-1971; 1980; 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Convention Materials, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Convention to Eliminate All Forms of Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW), 2009-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Collaboration, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: General, 1969-1975; 1981-1987; 2001-2014; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Thank You, 1969-1987; 1991-1995; 2004-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Deceased Members, 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 2: 10th Annual Conference, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 2: 23rd Annual Conference, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 2: 24th Annual Conference, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 2: 25th Annual Conference, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 2: 33rd Annual Conference (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 2: 33rd Annual Conference (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 2: 41st Conference, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 2: 43rd Annual Conference, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 2: 44th Annual Conference, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 2: 45th Annual Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 2: 52nd Fall Conference, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 2: 53rd Fall Conference, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 2: Conference, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 2: Workshop, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 2: Workshop - Albany, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 2: Workshop - Ogdensburg, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 2: Workshop - Oneida, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - District 2: Workshop - Rome, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - District 2: Workshop - Schenectady, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - District 4: 44th Conference, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Frances Woodward/Helena Y. Roscoe, 1962; 1997; 2015 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Friendship Club, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Girls' Club of Albany, New York, 1974; 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Golden Z Club, 1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Governor's Newsletter, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Governor's Report and Workshop, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Helen Cramer, 1969; 1973; 1982; 2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Helen Flicker Middleworth, 1960; 1968; 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Helena Roscoe and Frances Woodward Nursing Award, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Honorable Victoria A Graffeo, 2000-2001; 2015 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - International Relations, 1965-1968; 1970; 1999; 2007-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Jean Coon, 1982; 2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Jean M. Coon Humanitarian Award, 1996; 2008-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Karen Jones, 1982; 2005; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Kathryn Karl, 1967-1971; 1998
  - Kathryn "Kay" Minnock, 1975; 1987; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Keychain, Undated (Oversize 2)
  - Koinonia Primary Care, 2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - The Legal Project, 2007; 2009; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Lifetime Achievement Award, 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Lois Skuse, 1981; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Lois Wilson, 1974; 2000-2004; 2011-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Louise Gerry, 1957; 1962; 1973; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Martha Brown, 1969; 1978; 1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Margaret Welch, 1982; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Mary Goode Krone (Mrs. Charles Sells), 1963-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Member Directories, 1946-1948; 1951; 1955 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Member Directories, 1952-1959 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Member Directories, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Member Directories, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Member Directories, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Member Directories, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Member Directories, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Member Directories, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Member Directories, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Member Directories, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Member Directories, 2011-2015 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Member Directories, 2015-2018 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Member Directories, 2018-2020 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Hospital Chapel Project, 1956-1970; 1986-2016; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Service Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Milestone Awards, 2012-2017 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New York State Women's Legislative Forum, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-2021; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Next Step, 1994; 2004-2017; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Notes, 1971; 2022; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Pin, Undated (Oversize 2)
  - Political Material, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - President's Message, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1981; 1987; 2017 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Proclamations, 1971-1979; 1981-1989; 2009-2014 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Programs: Scholarship Award Ceremonies, 1997-2013 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Programs: Scholarship Award Ceremonies, 2014-2019 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Red Banner: Colonie Centennial Parade, 1995 (Oversize 1)
  - Red Banner: Colonie Centennial Parade, 1995 (Flat-file 2)
  - Red Banner: Colonie Centennial Parade (Photographs), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rhoda Hathaway, 1967; 1979; 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Ribbons, Undated (Oversize 2)
  - Rita Cousino, 1985-1988; 2004; 2011; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ruth Miner, 1969; 1974; 1980; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Sandra "Sandy" Scudder, 2017; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Scrapbook, 1950-1951 (Oversize 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1952-1958 (Oversize 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1953-1956 (Oversize 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1955-1958 (Oversize 5)
    Highlights of Chapel
  - Scrapbook, 1974-1975 (Oversize 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1975 (Oversize 4)
    Amelia Earhart
  - Seminar: Albany, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Seminar: Kingston, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Service Projects, 1981-1987; 1995-1996; 2000-2019; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Speakers and Guests, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - St. Paul's Center, 2012-2019; Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Status of Women, 1963; 1971-1978; 1987; 2003-2019; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Time and Again: The Quiz Show of the Stars, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vocational Lunch/Dinner Programs, 1947; 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vote on Name Change of The Dope Sheet, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Woman of Interest: Helen Parker, 1945-1949; 1982-2017; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Young Women in Public Affairs (YWPA) Award, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Zelda M. Uthe, 1965; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Zelda Uthe Law Award, 1996-2012; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Zonta Candidate, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Zonta Club of Kingston, New York, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Zonta Club of Montgomery/Fulton, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Zonta Club of Troy, 1948-1950; 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Zonta International 49th District 2 Conference (1 of 5), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Zonta International 49th District 2 Conference (2 of 5), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Zonta International 49th District 2 Conference (3 of 5), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Zonta International 49th District 2 Conference (4 of 5), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Zonta International 49th District 2 Conference (5 of 5), 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Zonta International Foundation Pin, Undated (Oversize 2)
  - Zonta Sash With Pins, Undated (Oversize 2)
  - Zontian of the Year, 2004-2021; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Publications, 1939-2019; 3; 2.4 cubic ft.
  The Publications series includes both local and international materials such as: The Dope Sheet, The Albany Zontian, and Zontian, The Zontian Biennial Issue, Zonta International Program Issue, Zonta International Foundation Biennium Highlights, and Zonta International Newsletter. These publications highlight the activities of the Zonta Club of Albany as well as those associated with international Zonta Clubs.
  - The Albany Zontian, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Albany Zontian, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Albany Zontian, 2019 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Dope Sheet, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Newsletter of the Zonta Club of Albany, 1989-1990; 2011 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Zontian, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Zontian, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Zontian, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Zontian, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Zontian, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Zontian, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Zontian, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Zontian, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Zontian, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Zontian, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Zontian, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Zontian, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Zontian, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Zontian, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Zontian, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Zontian, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Zontian, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Zontian, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Zontian, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Zontian, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Zontian, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Zontian Biennial Issue, 2019 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Zonta International Foundation Biennium Highlights, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Zonta International Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Zonta International Program Issue, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Zonta International Program Issue, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Zonta International Program Issue, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)